How can I be angry with you?
you from all my anger
What is an exception
When revenge is over
I was trying to tell you
Why do you think such a fool?
I have no choice but to say it now
I
i very much
I love you
Park Dal-i
Soybean oil
Huh? In the cave of Inwangsan Mountain
Did you find Jimjo?
I left it all over the place and couldn’t find it, ugh.
That's right
Then you will have found a habitat for the wild birds.
Are you able to hold your seat?
That's Choraengi Tal
By exploding a bomb
All traces of luggage have disappeared.
Choraengi Tal is
Didn’t you say you were a manufacturing merchant?
There was one more person, Choraengi Tal.
Eh? But why do I look at it
Didn't you catch it?
Is he someone who is familiar with the topography of Inwangsan Mountain’s caves?
I beat out a dozen people
committed suicide in a cave
Oh no
What should I do now?
Choraeng Tal commits self-destruction.
The cave collapses
Because of this
Jimjo is dead
Chi
You're making me into a bad guy until the end.
Every time I save you, I just
It was cool, he fell in love with me.
Yes, that will work, indeed.
It's not wrong to say that
So you just stop there
me too
thank you for being alive
I'll stop here, okay?
What about your back?
Everything is better
Yeah? That's it then
Let's stop sleeping
Kid...
Ah, well, I’ll sleep like this.
Why are you hugging me so tightly?
Do you know? My long night?
I won't let you go even if I keep talking all night long
Please hug me too
Sohun is a cub
lure the mother
You killed Jimjo yourself?
under
Because of one woman
You have torn down the tower that took five years of work to build.
Yes?
Remove the body and clean up the scene properly.
yes
Young snails are less toxic.
I can't give a gift
Now there is no sign or trace of it.
The work of the Year of the Pig
It has become a secret forever
Mr. I
our moon
It's disturbing my sweet sleep, Mr.
Hey Mr. Lee
Hey!
Shhh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Go get that, get that
‘That’?
Ugh, no...
Oh my mom
Oh my, oh my, how can I...
Oh my mom, my mom
How can you be like this?
Oh my mom
Oh my...
Oh my, oh my, oh my...
My body came back too
Why do I keep dreaming of poverty?
Oh no
huh?
Chi
Now Jimjo is dead too
The Inwangsan Mountain cave was also in ruins.
What do you plan to do?
Jimjo is just
It will be a bad day
As a monster
The public sentiment was greatly agitated.
Celebrating the Sea Destruction Festival
Please appease the public sentiment.
'Hae-goe-je'
The sky was angry and fell
What do you mean by disaster?
If not
Someone dare
In this palace where Your Majesty resides
They say they sent a messenger.
Do you suspect treason?
The person who sent Jimjo to the palace
He's a traitor
This is it
The reason I made you unpack the baggage with my own hands
For good luck, it is bad, for good luck is bad.
Wearing a uniform to follow the 'regime'
The monarch is not happy
When wearing mourning clothes
I told you not to celebrate
The Chief Justice's intention is correct.
Celebrating the sea monster festival
I will stop national marriage.
No, that's it
What are you saying?
There are only five days left until the national wedding.
Are you stopping national marriage?
yes
The analogy between a burden and a national treasure is
I'm telling you it's not what you deserve.
Even the previous kings
Even in hail, drought, and bad harvests,
postpone the banquet
Even though it was stopped,
In front of a burden-like evil
Having a national wedding is
Isn’t that absurd?
Under the pretext of a bad death
Since the national marriage was stopped
Jwasang immediately reveals that Jimjo is a talented person.
in a reasonable line
will try to cut off the tail
Yes, I am Jo Jo, a former royal court lady.
They will drive it.
Jimjo Cave in Inwangsan Mountain
It is connected to the Cho clan's drinking family.
The drinking pot originally belonged to the seated person.
But the seller of this device
Someone else's name is written there.
Can I find the interest?
Jwasang teaches alcohol to Lee.
I need to find the voucher that said it was sold.
What do you do after finding the interest?
After that
Be happy
If you follow the left injury
This national marriage will naturally break down
Then run away with Mr. Bean.
- Brother
- Live well wherever you go.
Don't hurt anymore
Don't be lonely
What do you plan to do now?
It seems like the Crown Prince was caught in his ulterior motives.
Crown Prince Lee and Sohun
The smell of roasting sesame seeds
The whole palace is shaking
Even this national wedding has been postponed.
If Sohun gets pregnant
Isn’t this a really big deal?
Just then
My child has grown a lot.
No, I'm so leisurely now
Is it time to just admire?
one
Trees that grow higher than the ceiling
It would be right to cut it.
Then
I guess I'll just go, um
Huh?
Boy, really
Brother, you are someone else’s gift.
Are you dropping it?
- 'Gift'?
- Yes
Woohee trusts me and follows me.
Even if I can't do it grandly
I need to cool it down.
'Sik?'
Hey, what does it matter?
No, brother
Do you use a door when buying a house or not?
When buying land, do you use a prestigious name or not?
While talking about
Why is the story about home coming up?
Why are we talking about land?
That's what this wedding is about.
In front of the gods of heaven and earth
we are a couple
I can’t tear it apart carelessly.
Press down firmly and take a picture
That's what it is
Ah...
That's it
Is that what it is?
yes
- Really?
- Yes
Oh, really?
Did you wait long?
I just came too
But what is that?
Ah
I received a promise from my brother.
When this is over
will leave with you
So I prepared it
I hope you like it
Don't you like it?
If gold and silver treasures were good
I would have lived like this
If you only wanted a large army
You would have left long ago
Next time, not a gift
Bring my father's downfall
I can't leave right away either.
More than anyone else, the downfall of the Left
Those who wish
Because it’s me
Is there a way?
To the former manufacturing lady
Looking for someone who sold alcohol
The person who sold alcohol
Isn't it your father?
Before selling to the manufacturer
To the person called Yoonga Geesim
They sold it first
Is it a name you know?
No, I don't know
yes
I didn't expect to find it so easily
Anyway
The person on the left is the owner of the luggage.
We will definitely find out
But are you really okay?
Still, he’s your father. Are you really okay?
My father once treated me as his wife’s meal.
I've never been here before
All I have to do is abandon my father.
Upset
Just wait a moment, I'll be there soon
Brother, comrade, father, man
i will do everything
Yes? Do you have 100 pairs of flower shoes?
Perhaps the owner of the flower shoes?
Is it a centipede?
What are you talking about, Mr. Lee?
Well, don't make a fuss
Well, please bring some paper and a brush.
I have something special to order for you.
Um...
Done
Look, um
No, this!
Yeah, as you can see...
Isn’t the number 8 in the West Region?
How can you
Do you know the numbers for the West Region?
what? 'number'?
But in the middle of this
What is Paris?
It's a flower, Mr. Lee
Skewers?
Ah, silkworm skewers!
It's not a cocoon
A flower is a flower, huh?
Take a look, huh?
Here are the flowers in the middle, these two rings.
decorated with flowers
It's not a double ring, Mr. Lee.
Yeah, isn't it, huh? Yeah, isn't it?
you're right!
No, what the hell
Why did you draw something like that from last time?
Are you just feeling proud of yourself?
Is it because I grew up?
Hmm
I will give it to my Sohun as a gift.
To the best craftsman
Tell them to do their best
It's dazzling, ah
It's dazzling!
Oh my, it’s dazzling!
Do you like it that much?
no
This Shrup is pretty, Shrup, huh?
Shurup must be, um...
It's like a flower
Ah, where did I get this flower?
I feel like I saw it
What did they say?
If you do it, I will do it to you.
Shouldn’t you at least reciprocate?
'return courtesy'?
It's like three generations old.
Do you need anything?
Besides, it's usually because of three things?
In the upper chamber at all
Ha Hae-indi even set up a wardrobe.
It's sincerity for that person.
‘Sincerity’?
self
Sohun Jaga said,
How are you walking?
Well, that's it
What are you trying to make?
Could it be that you
What food do you like?
Hey, wait a minute
- What's wrong with this?
- Hey, it's no big deal.
I just brushed by
Oh my gosh
Ah, child
ah
Wow, fish oil, it's hot...
They said we just passed by
Among these ten fingers
What about five fingers or bandages?
I can't do it.
Well, I have to call my doctor.
- Hello
- Oh, that's enough.
Yunan said it was nothing special
- Quick...
- It's nothing special.
It's hard for no reason
Make something like this
It hurts, really.
No, you said to me
There are many things you have done
There are many things I have saved you from.
Do something to me
I worked hard because I wanted to do it.
You just keep saying things...
- Okay, don't eat it, if you're going to do that.
- Ai, ai
Is that so?
Oh shit, I didn't even know that
I understand
I gave up five fingers
Let’s taste the pumpkin porridge
How are you? Is it worth eating?
Wow, making it
I haven't seen the liver even once.
Mmm, it's delicious.
Is that so? Oh, I'm glad
It was my first time making it.
Baby, just stay still.
This delicious pumpkin porridge
It's a pity to eat alone
Could you please tell Shinwon and Sedol?
How about sharing it?
Is it because I'm afraid the price isn't that high?
I already finished one bowl at a time.
Ah
Wow...
Oh, I enjoyed it.
This is so delicious
I'm sorry about the last spoonful
Are you sad?
Wow, I'm going to eat it
Did you set it aside?
That's a good thing
losing
Just watching you eat
I'm full
I'm sorry
Because national marriage was suspended
It's not completely over
The son of Jeundaegun, Nari and Mr. Bin
What happens to the transaction?
degradation
Deterioration?
uh?
Why are you breaking out in a cold sweat like that?
- Wow
- Ah...
Oh, it's because it's hot, because it's hot
Ah...
Are your hands and earlobes this cold?
It's because it's cold, because it's cold
Write it down, just do one.
Is it hot or cold?
That's the...
No, that rough thing
I heard you ate two bowls.
How did you eat all that?
Mandeok didn’t even eat it.
What you are saying now
That rough thing
Could it be the pumpkin porridge that Ji gave you?
At best I thought about it
I prepared everything for you two.
What were you thinking...
Hey
Why does Dal have to be so good at cooking?
To cook you food
I didn't even enter the palace.
It was delicious, uh
Just say it
Why are you eating so foolishly?
Ah, well, what if it’s a little foolish?
I wish you were good
Ah, it was delicious
- It hurts less, hey.
- Ah
- Follow me.
- Huh?
No, where are you going?
From broad daylight
Don't follow me, go
It's jammed, it's jammed
What is this useless thing? Ah, really.
Love is about doing useless things.
- Hey, what is dating?
- Fish oil, fish oil
Wow, kid
Hmm
No, well, from broad daylight like this
In this enclosed space
Men and women sitting side by side, huh?
And so kindly
Holding both hands together and clucking
This is love, isn't it?
Ah, this is
It's not that kind of impure intention.
Purely for therapeutic purposes, right?
The original person
My body had to be warm to avoid pain.
no, not like that
What if you like it warm?
Don't just hold hands
Well, try something else too.
I already told you to do something
Close your eyes
You might be surprised
Ha, kid, what
Close both your eyes again
Ah, yes
Do whatever you want, okay, come on.
Just trust this Boryeong Hwata, ing.
Huh?
No, no, no
Ah...
No way
Ouch!
uh!
Right, right
Wow, good job, good job
No, no, uh...
Did you call me?
Oh, I didn't call you.
no, just now
Sedol
Wow, eh
Isn’t that why you called me?
Because I didn't call you
Bring a wet towel, Mr. Lee.
Sir, I always see things like this, really.
I'm so annoyed, really
Ah
Hey, are you still upset?
I'm not upset
Your voice was very strained.
I said I didn’t sulk.
I understand
I'm sorry for making fun of you, okay?
I'll apologize, so come here
Please wipe that scab off.
Write, no, ah, what are you doing now?
Why do you put your injured hand in the water?
Mr. I
Huh?
Ah...
Oh my...
Oh my, oh my
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my...
Ugh, uh
No, not even rice.
I eat well regularly.
Ah, already like this
I shouldn't fall down
No...
Huh?
What is this?
What is this, huh?
Why is this, no, my, my, my body
Why are you here again?
deterioration, deterioration, deterioration
Hey hey hey hey
That, that, that right now
Who do you look like, eh?
I am, I am now
Who do you look like?
That's right
Ha Ha and So Hoon Ja
No, I mean, Mr.
So I look like the moon now
Does this person look like me now?
What is this...
A, again, again, again, again, again
I am you and you are me
You're playing, again
no
Is this your first time dating?
Why are you all having such a hard time?
Well, I'm going to live alone.
I'm not kidding, you two
It's like living alone
You're making noise, Mr.
Two minutes
Have a good time
Well, Captain Left...
What is going on with you, Mr. Left?
Last night, Sohun Jaga
in a secret dungeon
Take out the baby jimjo
You lured the mother
There was a testimony
go together
I need you to answer the survey.
As far as I know
Sohun belongs to Donggungjeon.
Why are you trying to take me so carelessly?
It is a matter of national fortune.
Please give me permission, sir.
one point of me
Because there is no shame
There's nothing I can't do
Let's go
Don't worry it will come soon
secret prison and
The existence of the baby jimjo
How did you know?
Former manufacturing wife during my Nine days.
Trying to give me fertility drugs
to a secret prison
I have been kidnapped
I knew then
The existence of a secret prison
Baby Jimjodo
If you don't believe me
Please ask the Great King directly.
By the way, the Great Queen Mother also
Rumors of baggage that have been floating around lately
I don't know if you heard
Carrying the Great Queen on his back
Are you going to dig up the Gyesa-nyeon case?
If you do
Why did you lure the mother with the cub?
What is it?
Rumors spread among the people
The public sentiment is atrocious.
Catch that monster yourself
uncovering the background
Isn’t this obvious?
So now the sitting person is also
This person
Aren’t you investigating?
Maybe a traitor
To find the owner of the luggage
Thank you for responding to my rudeness.
Thanks to you, I am now a manufacturing merchant.
Now that I have a clue
Now let's start investigating
someone who is already dead
How are you going to investigate?
Wouldn’t there be a helper?
Maybe a traitor
The mastermind
Wow...
uh
How did it go?
Did anything happen?
The seated chair moves according to my will.
They said they would investigate manufacturing merchant palaces.
No, I guess my body has changed now.
Should I say I’m lucky?
Fortunately
How glad I am that my body has changed
Why did you come back again?
I have to wear these uncomfortable clothes again
What would you do if you had these legs?
- River...
- I can't even write properly.
rain
A basin?
My body...
My body is back
Boy, it looks like the water is right.
Ah, this damn body
Why did it change again? Why?
Oh, it's noisy.
Please be quiet.
I'm thinking about it now, Mr.
Sweet, if it’s like you
Can you be quiet?
I kissed you just once
body has changed
We only hugged and slept for one night
The next day my body changed
I am also a healthy man...
What are you?
It stings like this
It's okay, but it's okay...
Blood?
What's wrong, huh?
What are you doing now?
child
Now, now, just a moment, just a moment
Huh?
Sweet, huh?
Baby, wait, wait, wait
Ah...
What is it? Are you back?
Ah
Wow
Ayu, you’re pretty, ayuyuyu
Now, now, it was blood and water.
Jirang and his body are all covered with scars.
If you wash it with water at the same time,
Damn, like this
My body was changing, wow!
Hey, you Dunting!
Why are you clapping with these bursting hands?
I'm happy
Did you know the principle of changing the body like this?
Aren’t you happy?
Hey
It hurts, your hand
Well, it's no big deal.
What is this, a big deal?
It's not a big deal, it's a big deal
ho
Now
Think about it this way.
If you get hurt like this
I think about you all day
When I think of you
I can't even handle the affairs of the country.
If that happens
The country will be ruined, huh?
That the country is falling apart
Is it because you miss me?
Well, rewriting history
Well, do you want to see something like that?
Oh, these pretty fingers
ho
Huh? ho
You guys come here
I heard you were close neighbors.
Go to Hanyang
Just say what I tell you.
If you do this, nothing will happen
Well, I really
I don't know anything
It's calming
you should know
Also, do as I tell you.
It's something to do
That's how Do Seung-ji lives.
Last night, the nephew of Mr. Cho, a former royal court lady,
I unpacked and confessed.
Connected to a drinking family in the name of Mr. Cho.
In the cave of Inwangsan Mountain
It is said that he raised Jimjo.
Have you checked the cave?
It was blown up and blocked, but
At the drinking house
Connected to the bottom of Inwangsan Mountain
found a cave
If you do this, you will be a manufacturing merchant.
Are you a luggage owner?
It seems so
Uhm, if you do
Now we're wrapping up the Jimjo incident.
Please resume national marriage, my dear.
Not yet
Huh?
Maybe he had some rebellious feelings
You never know.
A careful investigation is needed, so to God
Please give me a little more time
Chief Left Officer
Please do as you wish.
For some reason, I have a left injury.
It seems like you're wasting time
What kind of plan is this?
Did you find Chorang’s body?
Still at the cave entrance
They say they couldn't break through
some more time
It seems like it will take
It worked out better
We need time anyway
don't worry too much
Just as you intended
Everything is going well
Yeah, I guess it's pointless.
degradation
This is Cha Eunwoo
As you said
I entrusted it to Joseon’s best craftsman.
You'll probably be satisfied.
Ah...
That's good
What I drew that day
You made it just as well, huh?
Why?
I heard you were wearing a plain white coat?
Are you wearing a green jeogori?
wearing this red skirt
For the same reason?
Draw it, don't you?
If you ask me, I said that.
What are these clothes all of a sudden, huh?
Is this a personal type or something?
Is that it?
- No
- So?
Why do you have to wear these clothes?
Are you so sanctified?
bribe
to you
I need to ask permission
what to say
Bribery and permission?
lily!
huh?
What is this all about?
Not straw shoes
Reasons for living a life wearing flower shoes
wearing flower shoes
leisurely walking
The reason for that kind of life
Ha, my flower shoes
I'll buy you over 100 pairs, huh?
To fill a room
I'll buy it for you, indeed.
Why is this in the middle
Did you leave it there?
in your dream
I put my dream in it
Is this also a bribe?
Uh...
It's not a bribe
gift
I am to you now
I'm proposing
Ah...
Not as a crown prince
As a man
To the woman I love
Please be my only companion
Asking for permission
my
Will you be my wife?
Lee Kang and Park Dal
To become a couple
I tell you to the gods of heaven and earth
Please
So that I can protect this precious kite
Please look down and see
yes
If you don't find me
This fate and Hongyeondo
In the end, it will remain unfinished
Is it that good?
Wow...
Are you awake?
um
I'm stuttering like this
Will you die without waking up?
No, that's...
Well, I understand.
You won't believe it
The crown prince of this country
The fact that it’s entirely yours
My heart will be overwhelmed
I understand
- Well...
- It's okay.
No, why are you like that?
My Majesty, come out of the palace for a moment.
Can I go out and come back?
where?
To him
She was said to be an eunuch and then a court lady.
Last time, they told me to do it three times.
Is it Sohunja this time?
Oh, I don't know, me too
If I just close and open my eyes
Something keeps changing
I too would break down loudly.
- Ah...
- self
You need to be careful about your words and actions from now on.
Usk, why are you speaking so suddenly?
What is it? you now
Is it already time to line up?
ha
My daughter is now a concubine.
But if you line it up like that, ha, aha
Oh, by the way
self
Well, the sun is stinging
Come on, eat inside.
Father
Even your father is like this?
Aunt
Tusk, please stop flattering me.
Let's go in first
Truly
the moon
Ha, no
Alone with Sohun Jaga
I have a story to tell
yes
Ah, um
Ah...
Are you guilty? Why are you just looking at the floor?
land price
I didn't listen to my aunt.
You've come this far.
I took the wrong path
It's enough to get out
I will create an opportunity soon
Let's go to the Qing Dynasty
I'm sorry
last night
I got married to you
Now I am next to you
I will stay by my side
Are you saying you and I have become husband and wife?
yes
So, Usk, take care of your father.
Now leave Hanyang.
The left wound caught my eye for no reason.
You might go into exile.
That's what I came to say today.
Oh no
Hmm, no
She even became the concubine of the crown prince.
Isn't it good?
Why are you so dead?
yes
A slave who ran away from Hanyang
I even reached Sohun.
Ah, what could be better than this?
You don't have to run away anymore
Oh my, hey, it's finally time for me
I'm going to sleep with my legs stretched out, okay?
Decoction
You shouldn't be in the palace.
Oh, does that mean you are talking about martial arts?
I'll go out for a while.
Hey, don't talk
Where are you going?
merchant marine adult
When was the last time you asked me to meet you?
Any news yet?
Are you sure you put a flue in it?
I put it in, I put it in again and again
But what should I do if there is no answer?
So, tell me the business.
riverside
Year Month
Eunwolgak Hongnan
강연월과 한양에 있다고
Please tell me
Um...
Jimjo Cave in Inwangsan Mountain
It is connected to the Cho clan's drinking family.
Jwasang teaches alcohol to Lee.
I need to find the voucher that said it was sold.
Write
This seems like an empty house?
Is this the right house?
In this context,
To the former manufacturing lady
It's the house of the person who sold the liquor.
This...
What do you do in an empty house?
Well, since when has this house been empty?
Has it been five or six years?
where? Where did it go?
I don't know, I heard he ran away at night.
'Escape at night'...
Well, such an important person
This is not a strain to just leave alone, tsk.
The Landman Murder Case He Ordered
This is an autopsy report.
As long as you keep collecting Jimdog gifts,
What do you do?
There is no conclusive evidence
Shouldn’t we do something right away?
Why are you doing this?
Every body swelled
The location of the red dot is
rich blood, phosphorus blood
Cheondolhyeol
They are all vital points
If it's a red dot
Did you do the hour hand?
Not a manufacturing company
It would be possible if it were another palace official.
exactly at the point
A courtier who can bast
underwear girl
That day at Jimjo Cave
Chorang Tal, who exploded the bomb
In that cave
looked quite familiar
It doesn't mean I came in and out once or twice.
let's go
I'll have to check it myself
recently dead
I don't have an undergarment girl.
What's going on?
Is there any medical girl who suddenly disappeared?
A few days ago, he left the palace due to illness.
There is one undergarment girl
Why, not long ago, Jimjo came to the palace
Hasn't something happened?
I left the palace the next day.
Have you seen him in person?
Because there is an infectious disease
It didn't come out directly.
I sent someone
Bring his records.
Just drink it all the way, okay?
Hey, take a drink
No, what the hell
The owner of that empty house
Why are you so curious?
Oh, well
He took my money
Something ran away
Hey, bad guy, kid.
Ah, my wife
You just wasted money on alcohol.
No, the slave who made up his mind and ran away.
How can you catch it?
- 'Nobby'?
- to?
No, I don't even know that
Did you lend me that money?
No, actually
If a slave living outside decides to cheat,
You can't even do that
give up
Even from that left supreme leader of the world
The slave who ran away
How can you catch it?
No, it's a strain?
The owner of that empty house
Are you saying that you are a slave who lives outside the house of Jwasangdaegam?
Convene the committee members immediately
Send a message to Jaune too.
In the cave of Inwangsan Mountain
We need to find the body.
- Yes
- I don't think that's necessary.
Brother
Yeah, not really
I was just about to call you.
Chorang found the identity of Tal.
We need to find the body in the cave.
What is Chorang’s mask?
Didn't you say it was a manufacturing palace?
Kim was a undergarment girl named Deok-chun.
Jwasang is the nephew of the former royal wife.
before closing the case
We need to find that body.
But the undergarment girl and the seated person
What does it have to do with it?
The girl's mother
Sitting outside the house, Nobi-ran
found the record
Maybe the slave's name is
Are you there?
how do you know that
He
To the former manufacturing lady
He is a person who sells alcohol.
- Let's go
- Yes
Yes, yes, it's been a lot of trouble.
I'm sure it's somewhere here
There will be a body to burn.
- Find the body
- Yes
These are Sohun’s Boryeong neighbors.
Oh my
Prepare your official uniform
I have to enter the palace.
You've been there for quite some time
I guess you were trapped in revenge.
You were digging into the Gyesannyeon incident.
I'll end it on the manufacturing line, but
Thanks to my work,
sacrifice
I think I need one more
If it's an offering
Sohun...
Sohun!
Baby Jimjoro
The way it lured its mother
There are many eyes that have seen it.
How could it be from the crown prince?
And you want to take it all
charge
Sohun
From what I see behind the scenes,
Wouldn’t that be difficult?
Sohun would have no reason to do that.
Sohun has no reason to do that.
The poor man has a reason to do so.
How did Sohun stand out in the eyes of the Great King?
Do you know what you heard?
With the abandoned poor
I heard they look alike
But that story
Who can believe it?
don't worry
So-Hoon becomes an outcast
Mouths to disguise
Because I already bought it
What are you so worried about earlier?
Yeonsim-ah
That's the heavy hitter.
Crown Prince's mother
lump
Did he die after drinking poison in his car?
yes
because of that
Poor Mama has been dethroned.
As the culprit of poisoning of Jeongjeonmama
Poor mom?
Oh my mom
With what gift?
Where in the empty palace
They said there was poison
Poor Mama, did you say it was a drawer or a blanket?
Pillow?
Oh, yes, that's right.
Inside that pillow...
Huh? Why are you asking when you know everything?
I know?
Sohun is with me
Receive orders!
How on earth are we
Why are you dragging me to Uigeumbu?
The mastermind behind the Jimjo incident
There was testimony that it was Sohun Jaga.
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's a name
You must come with us.
self
Let me know
Come on
degradation
yes
Did you find anything?
No matter how much I look for it
There is no body
Maybe because my feet are too fast
toward the entrance
Didn't you run away?
Choraengi Tali
A bomb exploded while I was in the cave.
No matter how fast you run
The maximum is about ten characters.
Ha, no, then
What, soared into the sky?
What, did it fall to the ground?
Wow
Hmm, 'about ten characters'
We must capture him alive!
Why are you doing this?
It's not soaring into the sky
Unless it fell to the ground
He probably ran away
There must be a passage
find the passage
Mama!
Where are you now?
I don't know either
Why is Sohun now, ugh?
As expected
Choraengi Tal is alive.
Asking for a seat
It was such a difficult task.
The Crown Prince is looking for your mother.
My identity is discovered
It's just a matter of time
leave
Don't worry about your mother
Your Majesty
It seems like this is your first time seeing it.
Although it looked a lot like the abandoned person,
This is Sohun Park.
Mr. Cho, the nephew of the former royal court lady
Behind the Jimjo incident
I pointed out Sohun.
Do you want to confess?
charge
How is it
What's behind the Jimjo incident?
There's no good reason for that, right?
Sohun Jagari
They say they need to avenge what happened five years ago.
He ordered the palace to be unpacked.
Wow
Why are you doing this to me?
I really don't understand?
Jiyu, five years ago
I wasn't even in this palace.
But Martial God's Revenge
What do you mean, huh?
Sohun Jagaga
known to have passed away
Because Mr. Kang is an abandoned person.
What, who are you?
Digest it
Ha, indeed
charge
There is another witness
Auntie, uncle
How do I get here...
Your Majesty, Bakga Dal-ri-eun
I'm not old Heo Ok's niece.
Suddenly in the winter five years ago
The whole family from Hanyang came down.
Five years ago
Ah, why is even the lady lying?
Land in Boryeong
You've been here since you were five, huh?
The false one
Your tusks, ask your father
Oh, I'm going crazy, really.
A face like a desolate person
In the winter when the deceased disappeared
What happened suddenly came down to Boryeong?
Do you really think it was a coincidence?
charge
Please take action now.
If So-hoon is the abandoned Kang clan
broke the order and escaped
Are you a high treason criminal?
It is right to be beheaded.
Proceed with Chuguk
yes
But where are we?
It looks like some kind of house
Bird habitat
If you only reveal that it is related to the left injury,
The left injury ends with treason.
Ha, brother, here...
yes
You found it
finally
charge
Bare feet without any calluses
These are not the feet of someone who has walked a mountain path.
Choraengi Tali
There was one more person
Is he someone who is familiar with the topography of Inwangsan Mountain’s caves?
I beat out a dozen people
committed suicide in a cave
What is not a Choraengi mask?
Of course
I have never even been to Inwangsan Mountain Cave.
Let go of this
Let go!
Hey you
I have a feeling of oppression against Ji.
I don't know why you're acting like this.
It's really you
Village below Mt. Bukaksan
In the cave next to the blacksmith shop
Did you tell them to raise the beast like that?
yes
Obviously under Mt. Bukak
In the cave next to the blacksmith shop
He told me to raise the luggage.
just now clearly
Cave next to the blacksmith shop under Bukaksan Mountain
That's what you said
Write, the village below Inwangsan Mountain
connected to alcohol
I heard it was a cave.
I think I heard that too.
yes
Have you all seen it?
This woman
You're telling lies
The very fact of raising Jimjo
False Indy
How can you believe this woman?
Isn't that right?
It's too late today, so I'll leave it at this.
Because the day is bright
We will proceed with Chuguk again.
yes
The Crown Prince is here!
charge
If you came here because of Sohun, you were in vain.
The fall season is already over
It's not because of Sohun
I came here because of the left side.
What...
Left Speaker Kim Han-cheol
He is behind the Jimjo incident.
Do you have a gift?
Inwangsan Jimjo Cave and
The house on the left is connected
I found a secret passage
Oh my, this
Are you also confused?
I was very embarrassed too.
Uh, I just
Find the passage connected to Jimjo Cave.
It just came out
What does it mean that Captain Left's house will appear?
I'm so happy
Why are you looking at me like that?
Uh huh
Yo, yo, this damn, uh
Don't you have angles in your eyes?
I guess I don't understand the situation right now.
Your master, now
It's not a lieutenant, it's a high treason criminal.
Eyes wide open
- Uh...
- Where are you, Jeundae-gun?
You did it!
Of course
Because I'm cool
Sohun
no
kill poverty
The day Jwasang was arrested
Pack only the essentials
Come to the greenhouse
I will run away with you
Why do I keep dreaming like this?
What is this memory?
Ah, good
From now on, one by one
We must reveal the evil deeds committed by Mr.
Sohun’s family
Catch it
Disturbing the family
Isn't it a foul?